[
	{
		"questionNum": "1",
		"question": "Who is the first Avenger?",
		"answer": "Captain America",
		"choice1": "Black Widow",
		"choice2": "Iron man",
		"choice3": "Hulk",
		"choice4": "Captain America"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "2",
		"question": "The Tesseract is the ________ Stone.",
		"answer": "Space",
		"choice1": "Power",
		"choice2": "Reality",
		"choice3": "Space",
		"choice4": "Time"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "3",
		"question": "What is Captain America’s shield made out of?",
		"answer": "Vibranium",
		"choice1": "Vibranium",
		"choice2": "Unobtanium",
		"choice3": "Plutonium",
		"choice4": "Adamantium"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "4",
		"question": "What species is Loki?",
		"answer": "Frost Giant",
		"choice1": "Asgardian",
		"choice2": "Kree",
		"choice3": "Xandarian",
		"choice4": "Frost Giant"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "5",
		"question": "Who does not disappear from “The Snap”?",
		"answer": "Vision",
		"choice1": "Vision",
		"choice2": "T’Challa",
		"choice3": "Starlord",
		"choice4": "Groot"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "6",
		"question": "In the Captain Marvel film, what is the name of that cat that plays a major role in the movie?",
		"answer": "Goose",
		"choice1": "Chewy",
		"choice2": "Goose",
		"choice3": "Moose",
		"choice4": "Fury"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "7",
		"question": "Which Marvel character said “We know each other. He’s a friend from work.”",
		"answer": "Thor",
		"choice1": "Bruce Banner",
		"choice2": "Thor",
		"choice3": "Tony Stark",
		"choice4": "Black Widow"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "8",
		"question": "What is the relation between Black Panther and Killmonger?",
		"answer": "Cousins",
		"choice1": "Father and son",
		"choice2": "Brothers",
		"choice3": "Cousins",
		"choice4": "Domestic partners"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "9",
		"question": "Why can’t Black Widow have children?",
		"answer": "She was sterilized",
		"choice1": "She's born sterile",
		"choice2": "She was sterilized",
		"choice3": "She got shot",
		"choice4": "Her contract disallows it"
	},
	{
		"questionNum": "10",
		"question": "Which character is the daughter of Thanos?",
		"answer": "Nebula",
		"choice1": "Valkyrie",
		"choice2": "Sif",
		"choice3": "Nebula",
		"choice4": "Mantis"
	}
]
